<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="error_unavailable">Unable to attest</string>
    <string name="error_cant_parse_cert">Unable to parse certificate</string>
    <string name="error_strongbox_unavailable">StrongBox not available</string>
    <string name="error_deviceids_unavailable">Unable to attest device IDs</string>
    <string name="error_out_of_keys">No remotely provisioned keys for attestation</string>
    <string name="error_out_of_keys_transient">Currently no remotely provisioned keys for attestation</string>
    <string name="error_unavailable_transient">Currently unable to attest</string>
    <string name="error_keys_not_provisioned">No attestation keys</string>
    <string name="error_remote_key_provisioning">Remote Key Provisioning Error</string>
    <string name="error_unknown">Unknown error</string>
    <string name="error_unavailable_summary">
    Attest failed. Adjust options in the menu and try again.
    A common reason for consistently failing to attest is the inability to use the factory provisioned attestation key,
    possibly due to a misconfigured device or a corrupt persist partition.
    </string>
    <string name="error_cant_parse_cert_summary">
    The certificate format is incorrect or contains unsupported features.
    </string>
    <string name="error_strongbox_unavailable_summary">
    This device is declared to have StrongBox support, but it is currently unavailable.
    </string>
    <string name="error_deviceids_unavailable_summary">
    This device is declared to have ID attestation support, but IDs do not exist, do not match,
    or the device can no longer attest its IDs. Adjust options in the menu and try again.
    </string>
    <string name="error_out_of_keys_summary">
    This device is not registered with the key provisioning server, or the server permanently refuses to issue keys.
    </string>
    <string name="error_out_of_keys_transient_summary">
    The key pool is exhausted. Please retry after networking.
    If the server temporarily refuses to issue keys, check for system updates.
    </string>
    <string name="error_unavailable_transient_summary">
    The problem is temporary. Adjust options in the menu or try again later.
    </string>
    <string name="error_keys_not_provisioned_summary">
    Unable to fetch remotely provisioned attestation keys, and no factory provisioned attestation keys.
    </string>
    <string name="error_remote_key_provisioning_summary">
    Unable to fetch attestation key from key provisioning server.
    </string>
</resources>
